so we are in week three of making
history in 60 days I'm going to turn one
of these hundred dollars into a million
dollars and everything's gonna be
absolutely documented here on my YouTube
channel on my Instagram telegram Discord
everywhere so you guys not only see it
and verify but also follow along so you
guys can capitalize as well all of my
trades before I take it during the
ticket after I take it everything is
going to be documented here in the
YouTube series you guys are going to see
my metatrader when I take the trades the
my effects book after I close them
absolutely everything we started two
weeks ago and in the first week I blew
the first attempt to it but then that
same Friday I picked it back up where I
made 55 in one single trade so we
restarted The Challenge from that day on
the new account where then we took the
155 dollars to 2 700 in one single week
and last week I almost blew the account
I was probably three four hundred
percent of doing it but we managed to
survive and this is week three so join
me as we make history and capitalize off
of these Market predictions as well
let's start this challenge
all right what is up guys so it is
currently Monday 9 27 in the morning as
of right now so I'm gonna show you guys
how the trays that we broke down
yesterday have happened perfectly to the
T how I entered the trade that I entered
which I predicted yesterday not only
with my students but you guys here on
YouTube as well and on top of that the
next trade that I'm going to be looking
to take this week with the same ones we
just broke down right so let's do it all
right so as you guys can see as of right
now we got all three phones lined up so
we got in GBP CAD Buys so this I don't
know if you guys saw week two but on
week two we've been literally explaining
this trade since the beginning of the
challenge I've been explaining however
they've been looking for buys here but
I've been looking for buyers at the
break and retest of this so here once
again we got the break and retest how we
did here but here I didn't see the entry
signal how I like it right here so this
is where I went down to the lower time
frames one hour 30 minute time frame and
I entered based off of that beautiful
one hour bullish golfing Candlestick
absolutely right here got a little nice
pullback after and as of right now we
are still in very little profit but I
like the fact how this body has closed
above this structure right here that
indicates that we still have a lot of
upside potential so this trade is
looking solid this trade keeps going up
there's a very volatile pair we can have
a lot of profit made on this next would
be Euro USD Euro USC as you can see we
were predicting the pool back yesterday
we were up here and then I was
anticipating a pullback into this area
to take the trade up so we haven't made
it all the way there but I have another
play that we can potentially happen
since its shifted structure sooner than
expected oh before that let me just
refresh the time let me show you guys
that it is Monday live even though like
you can see the market taking life you
see right here it's 927 or 9 29 Monday
August 2nd so as you guys can see right
here we're back on Euro USD you see the
currency pair right there Market moving
live so you're a USD I am looking for as
of right now is a little pullback into
this level to take the trade to the
upside so that's what I'm waiting for UA
USD because we already predicted the
overall movement on this Market which is
the rejection I mean which is the pool
back into this level so in the reject to
go to the upside and then next will be
AUD cat so this is again this is the
trade that we caught
um week two of the challenge we caught
this massive cell and then yesterday we
were up here at this high and I'm just
saying to you guys how I'm looking for
the shift of the market exactly how we
had right here the shift of the market
I'm now looking for the shift of the
market right here so I'm going to be
waiting probably for a bearish engulfing
Candlestick right at this area I'm going
to be looking for this Candlestick to do
something like this and if it does
something like that then I'll be looking
to enter this trade to the downside if
you notice it is looking exactly the
same as it is over here and this is a
beautiful beautiful shifter structure
and others to keep taking the trade to
the downside so this is how we are right
now in the challenge currently floating
in profit about 800 on GBP Cad and there
is still plenty of upside on this tray
and then we got here at USD with the
potential little pullback to take the
trade and then AUD CAD for the shifter
structure on the reload time frame in
order for us to take this trade short so
that's everything for now I'm going to
be here in front of the computer talking
to the students and just kind of
updating everything I'll update you guys
in the next hour hour and a half and
we'll see how we're looking so stay
tuned all right so market update it's
been exactly one hour since the last
time we updated the market so let me
show you guys we just entered a new
trade and then the update on the last
trade that we took so let's let me show
you guys all right so as you guys can
see right here this is how we are
currently looking in the market so we
just took the year USD we're about in
profit so exactly what I explained that
I was looking forward to happen has
happened right now as you can see we've
had the pullback to the area of Interest
exactly how we were looking for we had
this pullback to this level right here
rejected this level 15 minute bullish uh
doji rejection from EMA exactly what
we're looking for because of right now
we are currently a dollar or six dollars
a profit so exactly what I explained
happened uh let's see now if the
prediction continues to follow through
and then we have GBP CAD which is still
kind of just doing its thing looking
very very very solid still so as you can
tell the true first the time up here
um last time I did an update was at 9 30
now it's 10 37 so exactly about an hour
and the last time we did it so I'll
teach you guys how to trade uh goes in
the next hour or two so right now I'm
gonna probably have some breakfast maybe
or just maybe look at it for another 15
minutes and then I'll head out the
office so stay tuned and I'll update you
guys all right so market update it's two
o'clock in the afternoon so it's a
couple hours uh since the last time we
updated it let me show you guys how the
market is looking right now so so as you
guys can tell we are up about 1300 on
all the trades on all three phones all
right so we're gonna go get a haircut
right now Eric just pulled up for those
of you guys that don't know I get a
haircut every single week so whether
it's either Monday or Sunday I get a
haircut every single week and I just
realized yesterday having a full-time
Barber essentially cost me a thousand
dollars a month because I pay him 200
250 bucks to come every single week cut
me up here I just don't want to go to
the barber shop sit there and wait let's
have the boy Eric put up and like I'll
cheat on my trading plan but I won't
cheat on my barber so you know
so trade update we lost on Euro USD we
lost about a hundred and eighty two
dollars on this trade
um devastating that we lost this right
now just kidding because we caught
another trade on AUD CAD you guys can
see right here that we are currently up
a hundred and fifty dollars on the exact
trade that I was explaining earlier this
morning so let me show you exactly what
happened so Euro USD we got stopped out
simply because our stop-loss was too
tight like as you can see right now this
thing is going to keep heading to the
upside I strongly do believe that this
has big side upside potential we just
got Wicked out which it is fine but we
ended up getting into AUD CAD because
this is exactly what I explained to
happen earlier this morning I was
explaining or earlier this week I
explained the moment we break under this
line right here I'm gonna wait for the
retest to themselves I didn't enter here
because I was focusing on Euro USD but
then I entered here because we got a
beautiful inch signal on the lower time
frame as you guys can tell we have a
beautiful shift of structure right here
left head right shoulder I should have
entered a little bit higher but it's
okay it happens what matters is that we
got into the trade so as of right now I
strongly do believe that we're going to
continue heading to the downside but I
think we're going to have a pullback
into this area here before actually
continuing the cells to the downside so
I'm going to keep Center for getting
this trade which we are currently up a
hundred and sixty one dollars as of
right now and then last but not least we
got GBP CAD which we are still up a
thousand dollars on this trade so you
guys can see here GDP CAD uh still very
much in profit the only thing I don't
like about gpp CAD is that it didn't
close above this line that I wanted this
Candlestick to close above so as of
right now that's the only thing that is
turning me off and I'm anticipating the
price to pull back a little bit deeper
than expected surprise can come back
anywhere and say here before heading to
the upside as you can tell I have my
alarm set right here so the price does
do that and notifies me and I react on
price there so as right now little
workout on Euro USD I still think it's
gonna head up to the upside and then AUD
card we are currently in it as of right
now I might add some position so I'll
update you guys either in the next
couple of hours while we're trading
London or if not I'll update you guys in
the morning so catch you guys soon
all right so market update it is
currently 9 30 in the morning so let's
check out how the trades went from last
night to right now we didn't add any
more positions but we might very soon so
let me show you guys because of right
now you can see this is how we are
looking at the account same account
balance obviously everywhere so AUD cod
we're around break even and GBP CAD is
just doing its thing literally like
getting us up there so we have a
positive Equity five thousand dollars so
let me show you guys exactly what
happened with AED CAD which is pretty
much what I predicted and then GBP CAD
it continued to go to the upside better
for me but I expected a bigger pullback
so let me show you so AUD card right now
last night where we were looking at it
it was around this area right here and
then we were expecting for them people
back in to then this area so we had the
pool back I didn't manage to get an
entry there and then it just kept
heading to the downside which we
obviously figured it should keep going
down but then now in New York session in
the morning it pulled back up to then
retest this area of Interest which is
very well respected whenever we're above
we're heading up whenever we're above
we're heading up whenever we're under
we're heading down when we're above we
head up and now we're under so we should
continue to head to the downside so I'm
going to keep holding this trade but if
it gives me a clean rejection and a
clean bearish engulfing Candlestick
which would look something like this I
would then be adding an entry to this
position right because I went very low
risk on this and then gvp CAD which is
currently right now giving us the
majority of the profit which is the one
that we've been anticipating for almost
two weeks now we then pretty much
retested and now we've been continuing
heading to the upside yesterday I
anticipated that we were going to pull
back into this area right here so then
continuing going to the upside we didn't
do that we just kept going up which
honestly like better for me you know
less stress less draw than we got to
stick through
um but I do believe we are going to stop
at a period of Point very very soon as
we've done in the past so I'm just going
to keep my eye on it I might close some
of the profits on it because we are up
pretty much double the account on just
that trade alone and then I will
continue my efforts and my focus on AUD
cat which currently right now it's
having a rejection camera stick in the
lower time frame so
um yesterday we took our first official
loss and uh luckily we went low risk had
a stop loss in place oh let me show you
how that trade played out so the Euro
USD which is our first official loss on
this account this is why you have to
have a solid stop loss even if I did put
my stop loss here where I wanted to put
it it would have still hit it we were
just wrong with this Market as a whole
temporarily I think that we are going to
still continue to head to the upside if
we reject this area here and then we
start coming together so this is the
original area of Interest where I was
looking to buy early in the week but
um not 100 sure if I still want to be
interested in that trade I'll just put
my efforts into the other ones where I'm
currently working so just to show you
guys the time it is currently right now
nine in the morning Miami time so we'll
hit Refresh on it one more time and uh
we'll update you guys in the in the next
like two three hours to see how it goes
so update you guys I had to show you
guys in my effects book how it's going
this is how a loss looks like on the
account so as of right now this is the
book chart on the account we were up
very well thousand percent which sounds
crazy and then now we did that a little
bit if you come over here and you look
at these numbers as you can tell this is
the same exact account that we're doing
right now we have a live market update
and today we technically lost about six
percent and this is the 100 of us that
we took on Euro USD so right now seven
trades close on the account and we have
a total of a 71 win rate and obviously
these are just all the basic stats but
so far this is how the account is
looking and
um I'm very very excited to see see how
this trade right here closes so we'll
update you guys in like another hour or
two no no cap on the game right now
Huracan by the way I gave one away
we got this
this is yours
that's not motivation to you I don't
know what it is
surrounded around like-minded people
that's motivation so I haven't left the
house all day and it's currently one
o'clock in the afternoon we're gonna do
a little quick walk around the
neighborhood and then we're gonna eat
and then after that we're gonna go hit
the gym get some boxing in I haven't
boxed in a while so we're gonna get back
into the cardio get back into the Rhythm
and then after that come back home see
how the trades are doing so see you guys
at the agenda too hopefully I don't get
knocked out
18 hour fast the reason why I've lost 10
pounds is because of the fast not
because of anything else I still eat
whatever I want but I just eat what I'm
supposed to
be
[Music]
so we just got here right now
but we got to do what we gotta do so
let's go ahead
so trade up there right now we are
currently up about 1700 so I think we
were up about 2500 let me show you guys
how the trades are running right now so
GBP car which is the one giving us the
biggest profit as of right now we are
currently having the pullback as
expected as long as we close above that
Daily Line right there which would be
that daily structure we should be fine
and the next day we should keep heading
to the upside next we have AUD CAD which
as of right now it's looking decent I
didn't add the trade just because they
don't want to over expose myself on this
one trade like we're already up in hella
profit and the other trade and I don't
want to trade through the cad pairs
against each other so right now I'm very
much still in this trade and if the
daily Candlestick closes like this I am
very very very confident that the next
day will fill that Wick and keep heading
to the downside so GDP card still going
to keep holding and AUD CAD I'm gonna
stay holding as well right now price is
just taking the sweet time live update
right now so we'll check up with you
guys in like four or five hours as soon
as we get back home all right all right
what we got what we got what we got
look at that
I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm ready to go
I'm ready to go look at your tuna
looking beautiful let's go so we started
down here your Mac and Cheese your meat
sauce you have some penne pasta you got
your beef stew you got your herb roasted
potatoes you have your cajun chicken
alfredo with spinach I didn't give you
that much mashed potatoes I gave you a
bunch last week but so I split it here
because you had a bunch of Thai food
here's your asparagus this is what I'm
excited about my friend I did a lasagna
for you and this is beef and spinach
okay just to throw some stuff in there
these here are the chicken cordon bleu
so it's the pan-seared chicken with the
cheese and then I went ahead and made
some prosciutto and crispied it on the
top so you're gonna dig that right there
man have this with those mash and
there's your chicken cacciatore and
again your tuna's coming out right now
my friend you're gonna be ready ready to
go
yeah
guys good morning it is Monday uh
Wednesday it is 9 30 in the morning
first of all big shout out to the
student that gave me this in the London
meet and greet um every single time I do
these events where I just meet Traders
and just get to know you guys and
provide value you guys always give your
gifts so thank you so much for the guy
that gave me it's an Emirates Jersey but
with that being said let's update you
guys on the trade from last night and
make sure to pay attention because
there's a big big lesson in what I well
there's two reasons why I did it one
because I'm a very experienced Trader
and I've seen this hundreds of times and
the second is because it was very low
risk so make sure you guys pay attention
so this is currently how we are looking
right now on the accounts we are up 2500
on GBP CAD but still any loss on 80k so
some of you guys may be wondering why
didn't I get stopped out on the trade
because the trade my stock loss was
around here and let me explain so as you
guys can tell the next daily Candlestick
we had a huge Wick and I was
anticipating that we would fill that
Wick as we've done many times in the
past but that Wick right there in order
for us to fill it we kind of have to
create this momentum to the upside so
this line right here is the last daily
Wick which is that Wick right there let
me take off all the time so you guys see
it which is that point right there so
this is where I go down to the one hour
time frame and on the one hour time
frame I see that the one hour has broken
above and is retesting the wick which is
also a little bit of structure around
here strategically this happened at a
time that is right before the beginning
of London session you see right there
it's 1am and London starts right at 3 4
a.m so this is where I'm like all right
cool I know what's about to happen in
London it's gonna have a quick Spike to
get started and then the actual London
it's going to have the push down so this
is due to my experience I then adjusted
my stop loss to this High Point right
here which it literally only adds about
10 Pips To My Style loss and then this
10 pip to my stop loss gives me enough
breathing room to enter the trade due to
the London session that's about to come
in and realistically since I only have a
Tula on this trade an extra 10 Pips
wouldn't be nowhere near as much of an
exposure for the account as if it were I
would be doing a lot size so I did it
because this original stop loss that I
positioned here was due to this entry
point right here which it was supposed
to keep going down with momentum that's
why it was such a tight stop loss but
now when the market comes back into this
area this is now a completely different
ballgame the market changes very fast
you got to learn how to react and adapt
that's exactly what I did I just simply
reacted and adapted and I moved my stop
loss up for the session being wasn't a
high risk and I continued to set and
forget so as of right now we came back
into around entry level we're counting
it down about a hundred fifty dollars on
this trade which honestly I just might
close it where we are right now because
I am seeing some interesting rejection
from that box right there from that area
of Interest where we are currently
rejecting from so in the next 30 40
minutes I'm going to determine whether I
close or not and then next we have GBP
pad which it's pretty much working as of
right now perfectly we have retested our
area of Interest which is this next
daily structure point right here we've
retested it perfectly
um this continuing the higher low and
higher high Market this is the beauty of
my style of trading like once you get a
trend and once you get a very nice entry
signal all you have to do is just set
and forget so this right here is how we
are currently looking
um if anything I'm going to potentially
enter a new trade if we break out from
this area right here and we give me a
little clean entry signal to take this
trade lock so I'm just going to keep my
eye out on this for now and then AUD CAD
I might just close at where we are right
now and if we do close out where we are
right now I can potentially enter a new
entry if we manage to then break and
retest under this line right here so
I'll be keeping you guys updated and
stay tuned alright so market update the
daily Candlestick has officially closed
and I closed the GBP cache position
probably like two three hours ago so let
me show you guys how it's looking so
this is the my effects book on mobile
you guys can see here how the p l chart
is looking you guys can see right here
what we are currently up on the account
the current balance is
4421 and the last update was 11 minutes
ago as you can tell these are the live
results and then we are still in the AUD
CAD trade so let me explain to you guys
why I got out of this trade which is the
winning trade that we were in that was
making us the majority of the profit and
why I closed on AUD card so let me
explain to you guys so this is GB CAD
this is the one that this is the trade
that just made us a thousand and this
trade right here I closed right at this
level simply because it was pulling back
into this area and as we were pulling
back I didn't like like the fact how
this one hour Candlestick closed under
this structure point right here I saw
this right here as a lower high and
whenever you get a lower high you're
destined to get a lower low the market
shift to the downside when you get a
higher high the market is going to shift
to the upside and obviously if we are
bullish on this trade and we have this
type of Market shift it's gonna create a
lower low so I closed right at the high
of this Wick and basically I'm going to
be looking to get back into this trade
either if we come back deeper into this
area or if we break and retest above
here so there's two different scenarios
that we can wait for we can wait for
price to dip back a little bit more into
this area to then give us our entry
signal to then take the tray long or we
can simply wait for price to then break
over this area retest it and then head
to the upside and then for AUD CAD AUD
CAD we are still in this trade as of
right now where we are a total of 200 in
profit so this is the one that almost
wake us out we moved the stop loss we're
looking at positions we didn't and then
obviously it's continuing to head to the
downside so right now the daily
Candlestick has closed beautifully I
love how it has a very strong rejection
Candlestick from this area of interest
but right now I'm just going to keep
Center forgetting hopefully this trade
can make us about another thousand
dollars um if we keep holding all the
way to the bottom here if this gives me
a very clean retest of the neckline of
this head and shoulders right here then
I will then be interested in taking the
trade to the downside I'm looking for a
pull back into here to retest this EMA
and the structure level to then go short
if it doesn't do that I am not going to
be adding a position and then last but
not least is Euro USD so you guys
remember what I was talking about
earlier today price came in perfectly
into the area where we were originally
looking to buy this is where we got
stopped out and then we've had a very
nice rejection from it so I'm very
interested in this trade because I like
how the daily has rejected but for now
I'm just going to Simply stay away and
only continue my focus on gvp Cad and on
AUD CAD so just to show you guys
real-time update refresh the website as
you guys can see it's 556 and let me
show you guys the myfx books here on my
computer you guys can see same exact
thing as my phone same exact numbers and
we have the
4321 4000 we have a little loss this is
with a little loss looks like we as of
right now we have a total of eight close
trades on the account for a total of a
75 win rate so everything's looking good
we're still on schedule my goals to
close at the end of this week was
obviously like 8 to 10K but even if we
close at a profit by the end of this
week and we double up every week after
that we will hit the mail in about a
month so in about a couple more videos
so it's looking good we're still on
schedule and if you notice I'm going
very low risk as I said at the beginning
of the first video so we'll update you
guys later on tonight if I end up adding
another trade or if not on uh Friday or
no tomorrow so tomorrow Thursday in the
morning all of the two guys what we do
so
I really want to do a market update
right now and this thing look at this
mini tiger
what the hell is that bro is that food
what the hell is that all right we're
just gonna we're just gonna get a cat
they said
anyways market update all right so we
just pulled up to the Cigar Lounge gonna
get some cigars Loki low on cigars and I
usually probably smoke one like once a
week but we're gonna have one of my boys
come over later he hasn't smoked in a
while so we're gonna give him one and
we're gonna get probably like a
humidifier so I can put them in so let's
go inside
yeah
so I usually smoke a cigar probably like
once twice a week I mean I'm Cuban right
like obviously Cuban smokes cigars all
the time I probably been smoking cigars
since I was like 18 with my dad my dad
who put me on so he's like you want to
be a man like
he's like yeah well here smoke this and
I hated it obviously like your first
take on a cigar sucks because it's very
like strong and you're not supposed to
inhale it so it's kind of hard to
pretend like you're smoking something
but not inhaling it into your lungs so
it's very hard to calculate in your
brain exactly what to do like it takes
about to like control your breathing and
I like it because it like relaxes me you
know like trading and just all the
social media like it puts a lot of
pressure on me and I don't do drugs I
rarely ever drink so whenever I just
want to chill or something go to the
cigar smoke it and then you know just
enjoy it the only thing that I don't
like about the cigar is a taste that it
leaves in your in your mouth right I
love the smell that it gives out like
even on your clothes it smells cool you
know it smells like a man but I hate the
taste of losing your mouth so I think
it's cool because it relaxes me and it
does minimal damage to like there's
minimal damage compared to like actually
smoking like a hookah or actually
smoking like a cigarette that you're
actually taking it in this it just stays
in the air and then you blow it out so
it looks cool like my favorite cigars to
smoke it's like this cigar right here
that they have this style of cut which
it looks like it's up it's pointy not
it's not that I'm not a fan of these
type of cigars but these type of cigars
for me it's a lot more comfortable to
smoke and that's like the smoke
distributes a lot better there so I mean
like the soap like the smell of the
cigar is though but I don't like like it
stinking up like the car seats because
then it sticks and says I have a
convertible I gotta stick to like the
type of roof that I have so I'm gonna
like
I just remember that I have that there
those are actually some Casino profit
nights that I had probably like a week
ago and I left the money in the car it's
not that much money but like I left the
money in the car so all right so I just
finished putting gas right now and
there's this lady over there fighting
with this car I don't have time to help
her but I'm just gonna give her some of
these profits to her so she can fix her
her car or whatever she got going on I'm
gonna try my best Hi how are you
you need help
uh but like you're already jacked it up
or not yeah as much as I could
not as much as you could
I mean when you own a Rolls-Royce
you're not supposed to do it you're
supposed to tow it
trying to make this work right now
mine does it all
trades
and changes tires
I actually hate you guys
no but this has happened to me before
and I hate it like this happens like I
drift cars like professionally sometimes
and it happens all the time
were you drifting or what were you doing
Center forget
how long is it gonna take you and just
do it
we charge 100 an hour
we're not we're not kidding no more
but I could drift this you know what I
used to do in this habit I would just
kick the jacket
we actually came from the gutter this is
how you know I bet half these rich guys
out there that don't even know how to
turn up a jack you want to do so cash uh
crypto we got one more thing
all right
wow thank you guys so much you guys are
blessing I gotta clean my ass
dude so you know what that right there
just motivated me we're gonna give away
the rest of this money in here so we're
just gonna find somebody homeless or
something like but I didn't even have
this money here like the Casino profits
like who cares you know it's not my
money so I've been in that position many
times before like obviously you guys see
that I drift all the time and my tires
popped many many times and I always
having a helping hand with help so you
know you got to give back to the people
and you know I mean it looks like she
works late night so give her some money
she could probably get an entire new Rim
probably a new car I gave her so the
rest of this money that I have in here
we're just gonna put up on random people
and we're just gonna give them the money
like that right there motivated me to
give back to the people as I always do
just you know haven't there in a while
so we're gonna find some random people
homeless people anybody and just give
them some money I have a math question
if you could guess what five times five
is I'll give you guys much of stuff I've
done five take your time five times five
is 25. there you go okay You Gotta Have
It
all right what is four times four what
times four sixteen
all right there you go all right you can
have it guys okay bye take care see you
again
okay thanks a lot I'm going to ask
people if I can turn 100 into a million
and if they say the right answer which
is obviously yes I'll give it to you if
he answers it right which is yes then I
can turn 100 into a million I'll give
them this definitely more than a hundred
dollars I can tell you that yo yo what's
up bro I have a question for you do you
think I can turn a hundred dollars into
a million dollars
you're concerned a hundred dollars in a
million do you think I can do it
yep you got the right answer that's for
you brother
thank you so much Alex Alex
and just like that seven forgot it's
changed people's lives once again so
kind of crazy that guy right there he
was just throwing out the trash
we just got some money for just saying
yes right answer I think he low-key new
I don't know well you said the right
answer so five years ago I was working
at Dunkin Donuts I didn't have nothing
now I've obviously made multiple
millions of dollars and money hasn't
changed me like I am still the same
person if anything I am a better person
than I was without it like there's a
saying that goes that money makes you
more of who you are and that is 100 True
like if you're a serious mean person
without money when you get money you're
going to be more of that you're a nice
happy person and you give back you're
going to be more of that when you get it
so ever since I've gotten money all I do
is give back whether it's content
whether it's money Education wisdom I
just continue to give to back and to me
that's what you know brings me happiness
because I remember like in Dunkin Donuts
if you would leave me a five dollar tip
like that would actually help as crazy
as that might sound it would just do
something if it would go for tires it
would go for gas it would do something
so right now that I just was able to
save that lady probably four hours of
time changing that tire give her money
so she could get an entire and those
random people like I think that's that
shows you character of um money makes
you more of who you really are so if
you're a nice person be ready to be a
nicer person when you get money if
you're a douchebag when you make more
money you're going to be more of a
douchebag money's not going to make you
a better person it's going to make you
more of who you are market update it is
currently 40 in the morning as of right
now so pretty much we're in the last
seven session of the week and let me
show you what the market has done let me
show you the craziness the market has
but before that let me show you guys
right now we have absolutely no trades
running on the account we are still
pretty much where we are at so let me
show you right here this is where we got
Wick out look at this this happens all
the time in the market this is what is
called getting Wicked out so as you can
tell the market right here hit our stop
loss earlier this week and as you can
tell this is where we went up hit our
stop loss and then we had immediately
pushed back down to the bottom of the
market where we were at the beginning
look at that humongous Candlestick Wick
like you can't predict this type of
stuff in the market and it will happen
and there's nothing you can do to avoid
it and that's a big mistake a lot of
Traders make is that they try to avoid
getting Wicked out it happens we just
simply move on to our next trade and
that's where you got to use only certain
amount of your account and you risk it
so as of right now I'm going to stay
away from this Market simply because
it's Friday at night and there's no
trades Euro USD as well you've had a
humongous Wick which I strongly believe
we can fill tomorrow so if this fills it
this would give us a very nice trade for
next week which we we can then have this
beautiful play right here that we will
then retest so if this Candlestick fails
this one that means it's going to have
this move right here it's going to have
the push and then next week we will have
the retest we'll retest the neckline of
the head and shoulders and retest this
area which is what we've been waiting
for essentially all week hopefully it
doesn't do all of that stuff on Friday
because if it does that stuff on Friday
then that basically means that we're
kind of missed the trade in a way but I
do believe that all of next week all of
these players are going to have a very
very strong momentum because if you
notice these markets are basically in
the exact same spot where it started at
the beginning of the week so that means
that it's building up
um like power or momentum so next week
it has a big push the market does this
all the time and this is where 99 of the
Traders fail because they don't know
when to stay out of the market and these
are the weeks you want to either stay
out of the market or have very low risk
and that's exactly what I did this week
I went very low risk and I stood out the
market for the majority of it so a big
lesson for you guys to learn and we'll
update you guys uh in the morning not
gonna take any trades I highly doubt it
but I'm going to update you guys on the
predictions of what I did so I'll see
you guys
all right so it is currently Friday 9 44
in the morning so exactly as I explained
last night no trades wouldn't take
absolutely anything and I'm just going
to show you guys what I expect to happen
for next week and um kind of like what I
predicted last night kind of happened so
let me show you a little bit so as of
right now you guys can see this is GBP
CAD as you guys can tell I have to do
guys we're gonna have a reaction from
this area down here how I expected very
a very long rejection from here I've
actually been cutting this pullback all
week since we had the higher high I've
been anticipating the higher low in
order for this trade to keep heading to
the upside I explained I still didn't
want to take a trade just because it's
Friday like this doesn't bother me even
if I missed it it's not a big deal
because we have all of next week to
catch trade so this is this is right now
just confirming that next week is about
to be an amazing week Euro USD same
exact thing we don't buy unless we break
Above This air right here so we're
coming back into this air Adventures I
have absolutely no rush to get into this
trade and then last but not least AUD
CAD this is the trade that we were
anticipating for price today come back
and re-test this area so then look for a
cell once again didn't take it doesn't
bother me just confirms that next week
is going to be an amazing week so let me
update you guys on the my effects book
as you guys can see right here we have
four thousand percent gain so far so
pretty much this week all we made was
like I think yeah see like this this
week right here we just made
um not a lot but realistically there
wasn't a lot of movement in the market
we have a total of nine trades and a win
rate of seven percent so this week there
wasn't a lot of Trades but that shows
you guys the reality of trading in the
markets not every single week is going
to be a trading week and not every
single week is going to be a great
trading week There's weeks like this
where 99 of the Traders they lose all of
their money or they even blow their
account because they don't know how to
stay out of the market this was a
perfect example of this week because I
managed to stay in when needed and then
I stayed out when not needed and I've
obviously learned this experience over
five years whatever but this is the
reality of the market not every single
day or every single week will be a
trading week and just because you're not
trading every single day or every single
week it does not mean you're not a
Trader just means the market isn't
giving you a high probability setup so
you have to learn how to be a skilled
Trader and sit on your hands into the
market gives you a nice opportunity so
this is a very valuable week uh luckily
we made some money this week even though
we took two losses that shows you our
wins are always bigger than our losses
and I'm very excited for next week so
let's check out what we're gonna do for
the rest of the day now I'll see you
guys next week alright so it's currently
11 13 in the morning Friday so no trades
today so we're gonna come to the
dealership now there's a new car that I
want to buy but they're being annoying
they don't want to like negotiate
through the phone so I have to pull up
right now in person drove 40 minutes to
come here just to see it by the way
driving 40 minutes in Florida or at
least Miami is far so I came all over
here to talk to the guys um and I might
show you guys that car I might might so
stay tuned
oh you've seen that video of that girl
that goes then you seen the video she
literally goes up to her car and she
goes
all right so I want to show you guys my
brand new car I can't even like instead
of forget boys we even got the seven
forget color ready to go let me work him
JC has yourself yeah I'm gonna text you
from mine all right these guys are
trying to put me on that deal but you
know what I'm Cuban I do this card
you know how many times I have been
still wearing cars I'm not gonna get me
again I have a question I have a
question for you do you think think I
can turn a hundred dollars into a
million dollars
you think I can do that
big Maybe
what
you think I can do it
No Maybe
it's possible right yeah I'm not gonna
say anything awesome what what is giving
you that it's amazing a lot of variables
yeah there's a lot of verbs there okay
so I'll get I'll give you some of this
just for answering them maybe
maybe if you had if you just said yeah I
would give you like 10 times more really
if you had a 3D printer Maybe
why that might be though the only way oh
I didn't say lately oh you're right
I didn't say that you're good thank you
did you say a 3D print yo we can stop
the challenge and 3D print the money no
week three and we are making history in
60 days I'm gonna convert one of these
guys right here a hundred dollars into a
million dollars we started two weeks ago
and in that same week I burned the
account but on that same Friday I opened
up a brand new one and then they're the
challenge was restarted from zero so we
can take another shot at it so in the
second week I turned a hundred and fifty
five dollars all the way up to twenty
seven hundred dollars and I was this
close to bring the account again but
here we are in week three join me as you
make history and I show you how I'm
gonna turn this hundred dollar to a
million dollar challenge so that is it
for week three of the challenge I will
see you guys back next week where I'll
be taking a hundred dollars to a million
in 60 days if you're new to the channel
or if you're a new Trader and you want
to make anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week as
a beginner Forex Trader using my Center
forget strategy make sure to hit the
link in the description below I have a
video for you that explains everything
in extreme detail I appreciate you guys
watching the video all the way to the
end watch us as we make history